Something's got a hold of me lately.
No. I don't know myself anymore.
Feels like the walls Are all closin' in.
And the devil's knockin' at my door.
Whoa.
Out of my mind
How many times did I tell you
I'm fallin' apart Right in front of you.
Can't you see?
I lose control.
When you're not here with me.
Yeah. you're breakin' my heart. baby.
You make a mess of me.
Nobody even knows where he went.
After that dinner. I can't say I blame him.
Heard he saddled Duke
with a full pack and just took off.
Weird.
Please tell me we are not
still talking about that man.
Staten is Staten.
Trying to figure out what's going on
under that hood's like falling up a tree.
It's impossible and dumb.
It isn't like him to just up
and abandon his ranch like that. though.
Are you kidding me?
Retreating is Staten's go-to move.
You know who doesn't retreat?
Make him stay.
He's like 20 festival planners in…
One perfect body.
He has shown up in every way.
Gave me this foot rub last night.
Was it a "marry me" foot rub?
Come on. am I right or am I right?
- I mean…
- You're right.
He deserves an answer.
and I'm giving him one.
As soon as I know what that is.
Girl…
He's asking me to choose between
an amazing city that I love and my home.
You expect me to up and leave Ransom?
We just want you to be happy.
Ange. El.
- Hi.
- We good?
We good.
- Hey.
- Hi. What's this?
I'm stealing you away for a date.
That's sweet.
But I have… I have to go through
the tips from last week.
I have.
She has.
Okay. Well. I also have
a vendor call that...
- Has been made.
- Already been made.
You guys…
Okay. Well. I guess
I'm yours. sir. Steal away.
Stolen.
What do you think?
I think you're making Quinn's job easy.
It's your best yet. babe.
I feel like it's missing something.
I think you're nuts.
Like here?
So you guys are… You…
You're like really not talking. Cool.
Anything I say gets run straight up
the ladder to Daddy Staten.
I don't feel like getting
into more shit with my boss.
His boss. the total scumbag.
Lauren. could you remind your boyfriend
I only took this job to support his future?
Also. don't finish the cereal
and put it back on the shelf.
Fine. Maybe tell him
to get his outdoor cat out of my closet.
Says more about your disgusting
closet than it does about my cat.
Y'all. enough.
Are you really not on my side here?
It's hard to be on a side
when you're both acting like children.
Fine.
I'm going to get some air.
I like the musician. …
Where's the cowboy?
I think it's a little on the nose.
This is fun. Where are we going?
Wouldn't be much
of a secret if I told you.
I guess not.
You did not just bust that lock!
Sure I did.
It's why I borrowed your bolt cutters.
- Are you serious?
- No. that's how I found it.
This feels very illegal.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Well. it's good to be
a little naughty sometimes.
So…
What do you think?
This is the Lone Star Theater.
I haven't been here
since it closed years ago.
I can't believe it's been sitting empty.
A few people tried.
but bringing it back up to code
is just too big of a challenge.
Yeah. it's a shame.
Wait right here. okay?
Okay.
God. it is still so beautiful.
- How'd you find it?
- Ummm…
Just
poking around.
Sneaky.
God. my dad used to love this place.
I had all my recitals here.
My mom used to hang out in the back.
but he'd always be right up front.
And I'd be right there.
I fell in love with music on that bench.
Wait. this is where it all started?
Well…
Good thing I tuned it. then.
No. you didn't.
Yeah. I did.
I mean. I knew it was special.
I just didn't know it was that special.
I've been sneaking in
all week just to hear it.
And the acoustics?
They're just out of this world.
All right. go easy on me. yeah?
Because I am no Quinn O'Grady.
Every little moment.
Walk me through the garden.
I wanna feel the earth.
Back before we started.
Back before it hurt.
Every little moment.
There are mountains in my mind.
Well. I got my boots and my guitar.
Yeah. I'm a bad mother-shut-your-mouth.
Well. look who's back.
You been cheating on me. Sam?
Never. Just doing business.
I've got a pulled pork and a side
of hush puppies fired up for you.
Thank you. darling.
And would you also get me a…
Ellie. if I didn't know better. I'd say
you're warming up to old Sam Kirkland.
No. you don't know better.
You order the same damn thing every day.
Well. let's make it a whiskey. too.
Must've been a good trip.
It was. Yes. it was.
So. one Kirkland goes
and another comes in.
Ain't enough room in this town. I guess.
It looks like that board vote
is going to go your way then.
That's where you were.
Locking in your backers. Okay.
I got what I needed. except one.
Hell. I ain't worried.
I just need one more big play
for the Double K.
Well. shit.
Good trip. indeed. I say that calls
for a Johnnie Walker Blue.
Make it two. one for you.
You know I'd love to.
I know. I'll drink them both.
Just give me a cheers. would you?
- Cheers.
This bitch is good.
I knew she could hook him.
I won the bet.
You bet against me?
No. I didn't.
Okay. So what now?
We move on him?
No. I say we give it a few more days
just to be safe.
- And miss our window? Are you crazy?
- It does feel like a window.
He seems emotional. cocky.
He's greased. Yancy. It's now.
Where are you going?
To call the Grease Man.
Didn't think I'd get him to open up?
No. I just…
Look. this is the point of no return. okay?
It's all going well now. but I just. I…
What? What's wrong?
Holy shit. He's kicking.
- Or she's kicking.
- He's kicking. she's kicking.
You should probably kiss me now.
Breathtaking.
Mural's not bad. either.
I get the pull of this place now.
I do. It's… It's part of you.
It's your home.
If this is where you see your life. then…
this is where I see mine.
You'd…
You'd move here?
Well. I've just got to buy
a pair of boots. but…
Just say yes.
- But you can't. can you?
- Oliver...
No. Quinn. I… I've waited.
- You can't look past Staten.
- Don't make this about...
How is it not about him?
It's always about him.
And it always will be. You know.
you're such an honest person.
And yet. you won't be honest
with me. and worst of all.
you won't be honest with yourself.
I didn't realize ranching was a desk job.
Think it was all bandits and moonshine?
Yeah. kind of.
Sorry. I'm looking for Lucas.
Let me know when you find him.
He's out today.
Yeah. okay.
- You were right. by the way.
- About what?
My poster… needs a cowboy.
… I don't know. It. feels
a little on the nose. don't you think?
Funny.
All right.
I need a model.
Can't draw it without a model.
No. it's not happening. Brigman.
Please.
- Feel like I should be charging for this.
- Quiet. I'm doing your mouth. Hold on.
I fucked up with Lucas.
What do you mean?
This whole…
Divide at the ranch.
Not his fault. He's just trying
to do right by Staten. I get it.
Just don't want it
to become a thing between us.
Why don't you… start small?
Like. fix something that he cares about.
Like his hair?
No. I'm thinking more like.
get Mr. Scratch out of his closet.
I think I got it.
- Mouth looks a little messed up.
- Can it.
Kidding. It's perfect.
Ash.
Your Highness.
- I'll catch up.
- Yeah.
You do know it's a Sunday. right?
Yeah. I just… wanted to be somewhere
no one would find me.
Why do you think I dragged the girls
through a Sunday practice?
Who are you hiding from?
My family. Jenny's back from college. Yay.
It can't be all bad.
You're the golden boy.
When you're the less impressive sibling
in every way. it's hard to be around.
Well. for what it's worth.
sibling trouble. sibling trouble.
You hiding from Kit then?
- Feels like I'm hiding from everybody.
- Even our girl?
Even our girl.
I have been trying so hard
to be there for her and support her.
but she is just like…
No. she has had a harder six months
than I could ever imagine. and...
Stop.
You get to feel feelings too.
Yeah. no. I know. I just…
Hard to explain. I guess.
Sometimes I feel like
I can't be happy around Lauren.
And you deserve to be.
So do you.
We should just enjoy it.
How exactly do we do that?
Maybe we start with this.
Don't you know time is always running.
Here. give me more.
That's something we can never change.
You sure this is okay?
- Lucas. we're fine. My goodness.
- Yeah. you're right.
Dude. you're unhinged right now.
Give it to me.
- I just don't want to get us in trouble.
- You'd be getting us in trouble?
I just know that you got
that UT scholarship.
And it's a great opportunity.
- What would happen if. you know?
- My God. stop.
Do not add me to your list
of codependents. I don't want that.
You can't take care of everything
for everybody. You know that?
I'm just being real.
You can't take care
of everything for Lauren.
Maybe you just got to let her
figure her shit out on her own.
Stop holding on so tight.
I don't know.
Yeah.
Yeah. maybe you're right.
Maybe.
I'm also really high.
Thank God. 'cause I am.
like. barely holding on right now.
Fall back on me.
Well. what do you think?
You hate it.
No. no. no. I don't hate it.
I don't hate it at all. I…
I love it.
Really?
Yeah. really. really. I love it.
- … Are you okay then?
- Yeah. no. I'm okay.
… Well. I'm not okay.
I'm in a bit of a fork in the road.
Two paths ahead and I'm struggling.
That probably sounds crazy.
No. it doesn't. Trust me. not even a bit.
Whoo. life's a trip?
- Yeah.
- But. hey.
- You killed it. kiddo.
- Really?
- Yeah. Really. really.
- I couldn't have done it without you.
No. I just encouraged you to submit.
No. that's not true. You inspired me.
Yeah. you've been carrying
this entire thing on your shoulders.
I figured if you could do all that. then
I owed it to myself to create something.
Thanks.
- … Okay. I'll let you get to it.
- Yeah. okay.
Hey. Lauren.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Always.
It's about damn time
you showed up. Levi.
Starting to worry you got soft.
What the hell are you doing here. Staten?
Cooking dinner for my little brother.
You look old.
Thank you. You look like a goddamn hobo.
Thank you.
You're welcome. I almost forgot.
Peanut M&M's.
- That's right.
- Son of a bitch. man.
And…
Some of the good stuff.
So what do you want?
It's been a while. I wanted to see you.
- Saw you last fall.
- What fall?
What. three years ago fall?
When I was driving to Buc-ee's to grab
a Coke and you were siphoning gasoline?
Was that three years ago?
Here.
How you been?
Hanging in.
I heard about your mom.
Sorry I missed the funeral.
There wasn't one.
Sorry I missed Randall's.
- Yeah.
- You…
You doing okay with all that?
Yeah.
All right. As good as can be. I guess.
Remember coming out here as kids?
Climbing the trees?
Sam would be there scoping for hogs.
- Like he's ever going to see one.
- He pretended a few times.
Well. look at us now?
Peanut M&M's. smoky scotch.
Like kings? Couple of Kirkland kings.
Something like that.
Except I'm not a Kirkland. Never was.
Well. you were to me.
Not to him.
That's why I'm here.
Okay.
Now we're getting somewhere.
He pushed me out of the Double K.
Double K.
God damn.
I used to dream about that place.
Wondered what it looked like
on the inside.
Well. it is part yours. Levi.
You can always come back.
Yeah?
How do you go back somewhere when you
were never welcome in the first place?
Granddad made you a trustee.
You know that. You. you still got say.
What am I going to do with say?
That's it.
You want my say.
Man's running the place into the ground.
But the board votes soon. It could go
either way. You could make the difference.
I know how you feel about this.
That's why I never asked before.
but I'm asking now.
Why?
When he's done with it. there'll
be no trees to climb or trout to catch.
The man is an agent of greed.
And what are you?
I ain't that.
Remember. this guy talks long and smooth.
Might jaw on about weather.
but there's more under it.
You got to meet him. Talk without talking.
You know what I'm saying?
Relax. I got this.
Cheers.
- Whiskey?
- No. ma'am.
I'm not looking for another two-hour nap.
I see Yancy's here. That's nice.
I guess.
His buddy looks high-dollar.
Yeah. not his buddy.
Potential buyer.
- He's selling Fuller?
- Trying to.
Why's he selling?
I don't know. I guess he needs the money.
Youse two are still together.
- Excuse me?
- Not as clever as you think you are.
You're still together.
trying to shake the wife.
Okay.
Shh.
We are.
- She wants money.
- Of course she does.
- No one knows about this.
- Nobody will.
Your secret's safe with me. darling.
Thank you. Sam.
Beer?
Hey. if you twist my arm.
Shoot. …
Got to change the keg.
This might take a sec.
Take your time. darling.
Go time.
And we're standing.
All right. don't forget his tell.
Guy's in a good mood. he refits his hat.
Likes what he's hearing. All right.
Take care. son.
We'll be talking real soon.
That's a nice pair of boots.
These old things?
Sam Kirkland.
- Bob Gaines.
- Pleasure.
Have a seat. Bob Gaines.
You're up. man.
Thought we were playing pool.
Well. just because we're in plain clothes
doesn't mean we're not working.
Stop staring. would you?
So. what are we… what are we working?
Probably something rotten.
No. makes sense.
What?
Nothing. I just thought we were finally
hanging out.
Andrews. man. we are hanging out.
Yeah. I know. I know.
Lucas?
Lucas. Quinn loved the poster.
Like. loved.
It was so sweet.
She. like. lit up when she saw it.
My gosh. It just made me so happy.
Kit. what is happening?
I was trying to take your advice and clear
out the closet. but tiny problem.
Well. actually. a few tiny problems.
My gosh.
Hello. little ones!
Guess it's Mrs. Scratch.
Yeah.
My gosh. I can't!
Can't what?
… I can't deal with your shit is what!
- My goodness. hello.
- Help me get them out of here at least.
My gosh. Don't climb.
Aww. I think he likes you.
My goodness.
Would you drink a ranch water?
They made an extra one back there.
Pop a squat. law man.
So you're Yancy's wife.
He's smart and pretty.
Tell me. where you from?
Everywhere. Where are you from?
Right here.
Scintillating.
How'd you like New Orleans?
I drank a lot of beer in The Spotted Cat.
Yeah. my Aunt Katie B
lived in New Orleans.
Well. she lived in The Spotted Cat.
- I drank a lot of beer there. too.
- Really?
Maybe we crossed paths.
What brought you there?
Roommate in juvie was from NOLA.
So Deputy GQ is a delinquent.
Reformed.
Shame.
I was almost interested.
It was nice meeting you.
Sidney.
Hey.
Don't be a stranger. Kai.
Yeah. that's right. Any records
of Sidney Grey in Dallas or New Orleans.
Bench warrants. parking tickets.
expired licenses. I want all of it.
Hey. while you're at it.
check the name Katie B. too.
One more beer. Sam?
No. thank you. Just water.
Something wrong?
As a matter of fact. there is.
You've been lying through your teeth.
I'm sorry. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Your boyfriend
hasn't been meeting with buyers.
No.
Y'all found oil.
Well. sugar…
I want in.
They're so precious!
- My gosh.
- I know. I can't keep them here.
I know.
Figure our landlord would take one.
and a couple of 'em could be ranch cats.
but I don't want to push it.
That leaves two.
You want one?
I want five.
Pick one.
No. I can't. It's… It's too much pressure.
Let's just sit here
and look at them a little bit longer.
Okay. You're gonna go see your friends.
Hey. Congrats.
- On what?
- Your poster.
It worked.
Yeah. it did work.
You got a gift. Brigman.
I don't know. I feel like the…
the cowboy really stole the show.
No. His mouth was all messed up.
No. his mouth was perfect.
… I'm…
- I shouldn't… We can't. The…
- Yeah. you're right.
- This didn't happen.
- It didn't happen.
No. No. …
I'm going to leave.
I'm gonna miss this.
Me too.
You know. I never thought
I was going to find you.
But then I did.
And now I have to go my way through life
knowing that you're out there.
When did you know?
Not until today.
I think this is the part where I'm
supposed to say I want you to be happy.
But it's not true.
Because I want you to be happy with me.
I wanted it all.
You'll have all of it.
Just not with me.
Yeah.
Just not with you.
That's me.
Don't try and steal my cab.
Selfishly. part of me.
Wishes there was a part of me.
That could be what you see.
Potentially. everything you want.
Married by a preacher
That we both know.
Least I get to lie awake alone.
Knowing that you're better off
With me long gone
'Cause I loved you enough.
To know I ain't what you'd need.
In the end.
And I left your heart breaking.
When I hit the pavement.
And I'd do it again
'Cause you might hate me now.
But someday. yeah. somehow.
When you find
That someone that ain't me.
You'll see.
That I loved you.
Enough to leave.
Yeah. I loved you.
Yeah. he comes out
of the tent in his underwear.
screaming. just hollering.
The fire ants. I forgot about the ants.
Shit.
Why'd it have to be like this?
Like what?
You and I are blood.
We don't live but a few days' ride
and I haven't seen you out here
since I don't know how long.
Now you're here asking me for a vote?
For what?
For power?
Money? For land?
Did you ever think it would be like this
when we were kids climbing them trees?
Now. hold on.
I'm sorry.
but there is a war that's waging.
and there is a hell of a lot to lose.
That Double K is my home. It's our home.
If you don't think that's worth
fighting for. then I don't know what is.
Our home?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
You know. the night my mother died.
I saw an owl.
Massive. white. Flew right over my head.
I took it as a sign.
So I saddled her horse. rode out.
Just rode.
As far north as I could go.
Out into nothing.
And the next morning. I found her.
Sitting on the edge of a lake.
A lake so big.
you couldn't see the other side of it.
I tried to get a little closer.
I didn't want
her to go.
But she flew away.
She flew.
I don't know.
into forever.
Know what your problem is. brother?
You still think home is a place. but it ain't.
Home is a person.
I'll give you your answer in the morning.
Shit.
Hi.
Good morning. deputy.
Trade you.
Nothing on Sidney Grey.
but the boys did get a hit on New Orleans.
One Katheryn Beatrice Lockwood.
Your instinct was right.
Katie B is a person of interest
in an open investigation.
What kind of investigation?
Homicide.
No shit.
Thanks.